Contact

abhiuday467@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ abhiudaytomar (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Tomcat Spring Apache

Abhiuday Tomar

Senior Full Stack Developer at Morgan Stanley

Essex, England, United Kingdom

Summary

Java Developer with 12+ year of experience. Advocate of clean and reusable code. Adept in agile development.

Skills: Java 8, AWS, DynamoDB, MongoDB, SQS, Lambda, Spring MVC, Spring Boot, Spring Data, AngularJs, Docker, Spock, Junit, TestNg, Mockito, Hibernate, Mysql, Postgres, Dagger, Retrofit, Git, Phonegap/Cordova,

Experience

Morgan Stanley
Senior Full Stack Developer
August 2022 - Present (3 years 2 months)
London, England, United Kingdom

Heartfulness Institute
Heartfulness Trainer
October 2017 - Present (8 years)

Funding Xchange Senior Java Developer May 2019 - May 2022 (3 years 1 month) London, United Kingdom

HSBC Retail Banking and Wealth Management Senior Java Consultant October 2017 - May 2019 (1 year 8 months) London, United Kingdom

Connected Money App (Personal Finance Manager).

Architecting and developing multiple features, using Spring Boot Microservices + AWS Lambda Functions.

Technologies used: Java 8, Spring Boot, AWS (DynamoDB + Streams, SQS, Lambda), NodeJS,

Topia
Technical Team Lead
July 2015 - September 2017 (2 years 3 months)
London, United Kingdom

Rated People Senior Java and Android Developer October 2011 - June 2015 (3 years 9 months)

mBlox
Java Developer
August 2010 - October 2011 (1 year 3 months)

Ivy Comptech
3 years 1 month
Senior Software Engineer
March 2010 - July 2010 (5 months)

Software Engineer
July 2007 - February 2010 (2 years 8 months)

Education

National Institute of Technology Tiruchirappalli Bachelor of Technology (BTech), Computer Science and Engineer · (2003 - 2007)